Now that we've blow dried and separated all the sub-sections, what we're going to do is go ahead and start with our finishing products.
What I like to do first is I like to heat the hair up just a little bit, especially just on the ends.
We're just going to heat up the hair.
Then what I like to do is go on with my fiber pliable paste.
A lot of people ask me why do you use that product before you go ahead and finalize and finish it.
I like to think about it as getting your car painted.
Do you know what they do before they paint your car?
They prime it.
Basically what this is doing for me is priming your hair and getting it ready for that last shot of color.
In this case, hairspray.
Does it make the shine stay more?
It does.
Basically what I do by heating up the hair, and you'll notice when you put it in, it kind of melts in your hair.
It's like putting butter.
When you heat up butter, butter is going to spread better, so basically that's what this is.
It's like spreading butter.
Does it help with the dryness?
It's not going to help with the dryness.
The moisturizing conditioner is what's going to help with the dryness of your hair.
What this is going to do is just help to keep its shape, what we're going for.
It's pliable and it's fibrous, and it gives you some of that separation you want on your ends.
Heat it up in your palms and just pull it through.
There we go.
Let's go ahead and go on to our next section.